zooomr.com 2008-06-22

# About Zooomr | Privacy Policy

Last Updated: January 30th, 2008

The privacy policy of Zooomr (hereafter known as the Web Site), is designed to help users understsand how BlueBridge Technologies Group collects and uses personal information that you provide when signing up for and using the Zooomr.com service.

## Collected Information

When you visit the Web Site, you must provide us with certain information to allow your account to function properly. When you decide to begin using the Web Site, you may choose from one of two ways to log in.

The first is by creating a Zooomr or Level9 account, which is in the form of a user name and a password. Other information, such as a display name and an email address, are necessary for various functions of the Web Site, such as password recovery.

The second type uses a technology called OpenID, which does not require you to disclose any information to us except a web address, or URL, of your OpenID web page, and a display name. A password is not required for OpenID login because session management is run by your OpenID web page, not the Web Site.

Every time you visit the Web Site, other information is also collected, which is your browser's user-agent string and your IP address. We also send information to be stored by your browser called a 'cookie,' which manages sessions and allows the Web Site to recognize that you are logged in.

If you wish to obtain a Pro account, you must provide us with applicable PayPal payment information through the Zooomr Upgrade page.

## Children

Because our Terms of Service prohibit use of the Web Site by children under the age of 13 years old, our privacy policy does not make a provision for young children. We do not intend to collect any information whatsoever about children under the age of 13.

## How We Use Your Information

Information that is obtained by BlueBridge through your use of the Web Site, such as your user name or photos that you upload, may be publicly displayed on parts of the Web Site in accordance with your account's privacy settings. For instance, images marked as private are inaccessible to anyone except the user who uploaded them. Meanwhile, images marked as public will be visible to anyone, including non-members of the Web Site.

BlueBridge does not share personal information (such as your email address) with third parties except in cases in which we are mandated to by law, such as court orders or subpoenas.

## OpenID

Because BlueBridge is unaffiliated with and does not control OpenID systems which may be used to access the Web Site, we can not make any guarantees regarding personal information that you provide to third-party OpenID services. If you are using community or commercial OpenID system such as TypeKey™ or LiveJournal™, we recommend that you read its Terms of Service and Privacy Policy before use.

## Links and Advertising

Occasionally, BlueBridge may opt to run advertisements on the Web Sites that supply their own cookies and that link to third-party web pages that are unaffiliated with BlueBridge. Similarly, users may post links to unaffiliated pages. We are not in control of the behavior of these cookies and web pages and take no responsibility for their actions or content.

## Changing Information

At any time, users may change their email address or display name. You may only change your Zooomr URL one time, to minimize the breakage of links from external sources to the Web Site. To ensure the security of personal information, upon account deletion, all information about you will be deleted within one week (7 days) except your IP address and user-agent string (which may be permanently retained in access logs) unless retaining certain personal information is pursuant to lawful requests such as subpoenas and court orders. Additionally, third-party entities such as search engines and archive sites may create mirrors or backups of pages on the Web Site. This is an activity that cannot be controlled by BlueBridge and may cache data such as your display name and photos for any possible length of time. We advise that users utilize a reasonable amount of discretion before posting information on public pages on the Web Site.

## Security

BlueBridge takes security of your data very seriously. All of your information is stored on a specialized server that is protected by multiple layers of security. However, it is also the user's responsibility to access the Web Site in a secure way. BlueBridge cannot be held responsible for data theft resulting from negligence on the part of user (such as browsing the Web Site via an unencrypted wireless connection, or providing one's secret account information to an untrustworthy entity).

## Changes to the Privacy Policy

As per our Terms of Service, BlueBridge reserves the right to change the Privacy Policy at any time, in any way, for any reason. We advise users to periodically refer to this policy so that you understand the current policy in effect.

If you have further questions about the privacy policy, see our Help page.
